<resources>
    <string name="app_version">Version %s</string>
    <string name="credits_text">App developed by Ferdinando Traversa for Wiki Loves Monuments.\nTree icon derived by symbolon, CC-BY 3.0 license.\nNavigation bar icons derived by FontAwesome, CC-BY-SA 4.0 license\nEnglish translation by Marco Montanari (@sirmmo)</string>
    <string name="error_geolocation">Something went wrong! Make sure you have geolocation enabled and restart the app or click refresh.</string>
    <string name="connection_erorr">A connection error occurred: %s.Retry later.</string> 
    <string name="generic_error">An error occurred: %s. Retry later.</string> 
    <string name="activate_geolocation">Enable geolocation to use the map.</string>
    <string name="no_geolocation_permission">Unable to locate you, you have not given permission to locate. Search for a city by clicking on the magnifying glass or enable localization from your privacy settings.</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="refuse">Refuse</string>
    <string name="analytics_ask">Do you want to share some usage (in particular, the app version when you start the app) and crash data with the developer of this application with some anonymous information about your device, so that you can contribute to the app improvement? The data will not be shared with third parties.</string>
    <string name="analytics_title">Usage and crash data</string>
    <string name="no_results_found">No results found! Try another search</string>
    <string name="minimum_char">Enter a minimum of 3 characters to perform a search.</string>
    <string name="upload_stopped">You have cancelled uploading photos</string>
    <string name="no_upload_permission">You may not have granted permission to access the photo gallery. Verify.</string>
    <string name="keychain_error">An error occurred with the keychain reading, please try again later.</string>
    <string name="signup_not_completed">Registration incomplete! Log in to Wikimedia Commons to continue.</string>
    <string name="authorization_expired">The authorization on this monument has expired.</string>
    <string name="more_information">More infos on %s</string>
    <string name="choose_mean">How do you want to reach %s?</string>
    <string name="by_car">By car</string>
    <string name="on_foot">On foot</string>
    <string name="by_bike">By bike</string>
    <string name="no_geoloc_no_route">Without active geolocation I am unable to plot a route!</string>
    <string name="registration_deleted_by_user">As requested, you have been logged out by the application. Reopen this tab to start a new one and upload your photographs.</string>
    <string name="registration_deleted_by_error">You have been logged out due to a problem. Reopen this tab to start a new one and upload your photographs.</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="server_deletion_not_possible">Your data could not be deleted from the server. Make sure to revoke the oAuth authorization. </string>
    <string name="login_info">Username: %1$s\nWiki: %2$s</string>
    <string name="your_username"> Your username is %s.</string>
    <string name="start_commons_login">Login to Wikimedia Commons</string>
    <string name="login_not_done">You are not logged in. Click on login to Wikimedia Commons to do so.</string>
    <string name="problem_do_logout">Something went wrong, retry later. If it happens again, please log out and log in again.</string>
    <string name="no_upload_until_commons">Before you can upload photographs, you must be logged into Wikimedia Commons.</string>
    <string name="photo_not_uploaded">Image %s not uploaded due to error.</string>
    <string name="photo_not_uploaded_with_reason">Image %1$s not uploaded due to error: %2$s.</string>
    <string name="error_please_logout">An error has occurred. Log out from the Upload Settings Manager in the settings tab.</string>
    <string name="error_image_upload">Error uploading this image, please try again later.</string> 
    <string name="image_title">Image title</string>
    <string name="image_description">Image description</string>
    <string name="image_date">Image creation date (dd/mm/yyyy)</string>
    <string name="error_date_format">Warning: the date format must be dd/mm/yyyyy such as 11/05/2005.</string>
    <string name="fields_are_mandatory">The fields are mandatory! Fill them all out before uploading.</string>
    <string name="image_queue_success">Photos successfully queued for upload! You can check their status in the settings.</string> 
    <string name="image_queue_error">Something went wrong and the upload failed. Please try again later: %s.</string>.
    <string name="update_app">Warning! You are using an outdated version of the app (%1$s). Go to the store and download the new version %2$s.</string>.
    <string name="info">Info about Wiki Loves Monuments</string>
    <string name="credits">Credits</string>.
    <string name="upload_config">Manage upload settings</string>.
    <string name="upload_list">Uploaded photos</string>
    <string name="infocors">Wiki Loves Monuments is an international contest that aims to illustrate Wikipedia and Wikimedia projects through photographs of cultural heritage taken by citizens themselves, thus being also a great opportunity for tourism promotion.\nIt was born in 2010 and is organized annually around the world, in more than 50 countries, from 1 to 30 September.\nIn 2012 it entered the Guinness Book of Records as the largest photo contest in the world. Each year, more than 130,000 photographs are uploaded.\nThe subject of the images allowed to participate in the competition are monuments, a very broad set that includes buildings, sculptures, archaeological sites, architectural structures but also natural sites and landscape assets. All photographs are released under a free license and published on Wikimedia Commons, the large database that illustrates Wikipedia (the 5th most visited site in Italy) and all other projects with multimedia content (photos and videos).\nWiki Loves Monuments is open to the participation of everyone, professional photographers or amateurs, with no age limit. \nThe Italian edition is organized since 2012 by Wikimedia Italia, an association that has been working since 2005 to spread knowledge and free culture in Italy, as a chapter of Wikimedia Foundation.</string> 
    <string name="site">Visit the contest website</string>
    <string name="winmap">Map</string>
    <string name="town_searchfield">Insert the name of the city...</string> 
    <string name="monument_searchfield">Insert the name of the monument...</string>
    <string name="list_section_monuments_header">Found Monuments</string>
    <string name="list_section_towns_header">Found cities</string>
    <string name="winsearch">Search by name</string>
    <string name="placeholder_show_title">Monument</string>
    <string name="upload_button">Upload your photos</string>
    <string name="only_september">Only photos uploaded from September 1 to 30 will participate in Wiki Loves Monuments.</string>
    <string name="osm_text">Driving directions</string>
    <string name="more_information_button">More info</string>
    <string name="wikipedia_article">Wikipedia article</string>
    <string name="upload_settings_welcome">From here you can control the settings related to your Wikimedia account with particular reference to the photo upload functionality from the app.</string>
    <string name="upload_settings">Upload settings management</string>
    <string name="login_start">Login to Wikimedia Commons</string>
    <string name="login_update">Verify access</string>
    <string name="login_delete">Logout</string>
    <string name="login_instructions">To continue, login or create an account on Wikimedia Commons by clicking the blue button above. If you have already logged in, click the button to verify that you are logged in.</string>
    <string name="by_date">By date</string> 
    <string name="by_name">By name</string> 
    <string name="show_monument">Monument info</string>
    <string name="photo_list">Uploaded photos list</string>
    <string name="photo_upload">Photo upload</string>
    <string name="index_header_text">Images already uploaded</string> 
    <string name="title_header_text">Images to upload</string> 
    <string name="license_acceptance">You can leave the fields as they are or edit them making them more informative. Your choice!\nClicking on "Confirm and upload", you accept to irrevocably release these images under the Creative Commons-Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 license, you acknowledge that they will be published on Wikimedia Commons and will be reusable in perpetuity under the terms of that license and you also declare to be their author. If you continue with the upload, you also acknowledge that the criminal and civil responsibility for what is being uploaded is your own.</string>
    <string name="confirm_upload">Confirm and upload</string>
    <string name="stop_upload">Cancel</string>
    <string name="monuments">Monuments</string>
    <string name="towns">Cities</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="search_tab">Search</string>
    <string name="settings_tab">Settings</string> 
    <string name="image_uploading">Photo %s still uploading...</string>
    <string name="license_link_text">License text</string>
    <string name="faq_ask">Do you know how to use the app? If not, read our handy FAQs! You'll always find them in Settings, if you need.</string>
    <string name="read_faq">No, take me straight to the FAQs!</string>
    <string name="no_more_faq">Yes, I'm an expert. I don't need them.</string>
    <string name="faq">Frequently asked questions</string>
    <string name="close_app_ask">Do you want to close WLM Italia?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="allphotos">Uploaded photos for this monument</string>
    <string name="photos_on_commons">All your photos on Commons</string>
    <string name="test_login_start">You're going to login to Test Wiki. If you are not a tester, please do not login to the test wiki and instead do a single click (not a long press) on the button. Anyway, the photos that are uploaded on the test wiki do not participate in the contest.</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>

    <string name="welcome_text">Benvenuto nell'app di Wiki Loves Monuments Italia, il concorso fotografico dedicato ai monumenti.</string>
    <string name="welcome_button">Prosegui</string>
    <string name="welcome">Benvenuto!</string>
    <string name="location_title">Posizione</string>
    <string name="location_text">Quest'applicazione necessita del tuo permesso all'uso della posizione in quanto gran parte delle funzioni sono basate sulla localizzazione. In questo modo, potrai localizzare i monumenti vicino a te!</string>
    <string name="procedi">Procedi</string>
    <string name="stats_title">Analisi e dati</string>
    <string name="faq_title">Domande frequenti</string>
</resources>